Finding Aid to The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Photographs MS.57
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1144; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 9/16 x 8 7/8 inches; view of 4 paintings on wallHandwritten on verso: "I 17a", "10" (circled), "OK 44C"
  View of gallery installation of four O'Keeffe paintings on three walls; 2 paintings of jack-in-the-pulpits, an abstraction, and an enlarged flower.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1145; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 inches; view of 6 paintings on wallHandwritten on verso: "I 18a", "9" (circled), "Show -Jan. Feb. 31"
  Installation view of six O'Keeffe paintings on a white wall; two New Mexican landscapes, two versions of jack-in-the-pulpits, and 2 abstract paintings.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1146; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 7/8 x 9 15/16 inches; Print has been mounted on the back of another print (2006-06-1147). Handwritten on verso: "I 15b","10" (circled); Handwritten on recto: "1930", illegible scribblings
  Installation view of six O'Keeffe paintings on white walls; two paintings of New Mexican landscapes, and four paintings of flowers. The most abstract flower painting in on the adjacent wall.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1147; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 7/8 x 9 15/16 inches; Print has been mounted on the back of another print (2006-06-1146_a). Handwitten in graphite: 1930. Graphite lines across print.
  Installation view of four O'Keeffe paintings on a white gallery wall; two paintings of flowers, two paintings of trees and one painting of a New Mexico landscape. Written in pencil on the surface photograph is 1930 and scribbles on lower half of the image.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1148; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 x 9 9/16 inches; view of 3 paintings on wall; mounted on 3 hole punch paperHandwritten on support: "I 16" "9" circled
  Installation view of three O'Keeffe paintings on a gallery wall; 2 paintings of trees and one painting of a New Mexican landscape.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1149; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view of 2 paintings on wallHandwritten on verso: "I 19b" "9" circled
  Installation view of two O'Keeffe paintings; one is an abstract composition and the other painting is of a New Mexican church with an adobe wall. A black diagonal line runs across the bottom corner of the photograph.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1150; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 7 5/8 inches; view of 4 paintings on wallHandwritten on recto: check marks and a line dash Handwritten on verso: "I 21a" "9" circled "Show - 31- Jan .Feb."
  Installation view of three O'Keeffe paintings of New Mexico landscapes with a view of painting of an abstract flower in the adjoining room. The two landscape paintings that are stacked have black check marks written on the surface of the photograph.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1151; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view of 5 paintings on wall; signed on back 'Show Jan Feb - 31'Handwritten on verso: "I 21b" "9" circled
  Installation view of three O'Keeffe paintings of New Mexico landscapes and one Pueblo style church. In the adjoining room is a view of painting of an abstract flower.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1152; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 6 3/4 inches; view 2 paintings; one has black check mark over it; Signed 'Show Jan Feb - 31'Handwritten on recto: check mark Handwritten on verso: "I 20" "9" circled "Show Jan. Feb - 31"
  Installation view of two O'Keeffe paintings, a version of Ranchos de Taos Church and a New Mexican landscape. On the surface of the photograph is a black check mark above the landscape painting along with a black diagonal line in the lower corner of the print.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition: An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1931; 2006.6.1153; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 5 7/16 inches; cropped photographHandwritten on recto: check mark Handwritten on verso: "I 19a" "6" circled "Show 31 - Jan & Feb Shell"
  Installation view of an abstract O'Keeffe painting.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 33 New Paintings (New Mexico) - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, circa 1931; 2006.6.1154; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view 5 paintings (2 cowskulls); Signed 'Show Dec 31 Feb 32'Handwritten on verso: "I 22b" "11" circled "Show - Dec 31 - Feb - 32"
  Installation view of five O'Keeffe paintings on adjacent white walls; 2 paintings of horse skulls, one painting of a thigh bone, one painting of a landscape and one painting of a flower.
- Georgia O'Keeffe 33 New Paintings (New Mexico) - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, circa 1931; 2006.6.1155; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view 5 paintings (2 cowskulls); Signed 'Show Dec 31 Feb 32'Handwritten on recto: check mark Handwritten on verso: "I23c" "11" circled "Show Dec. 31 Feb 32" "Abstraction"?
  Installation view of five O'Keeffe paintings on adjacent white walls; 2 paintings of horse skulls, one painting of a thigh bone, a painting of a landscape and a painting of a the Ranchos de Taos Church.
- Georgia O'Keeffe New & Some Old - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1933; 2006.6.1156; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view of 3 paintings on wall; one copy cut down; one signed 'Show Jan Feb 33'Handwritten on verso: "I24 b" "12" circled "Show - Jan .Feb. 33"
  Installation view of three of O'Keeffe's paintings; large painting of a cross in the landscape, the painting Jimson Weed and a painting of barns.
- Georgia O'Keeffe New & Some Old - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1933; 2006.6.1157; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 9 15/16 inches; view of 4 paintings on wall; sticky note GreenoughHandwritten on verso: "I25" "12" circled
  Installation view of three of O'Keeffe's paintings on a white wall; a painting of a leaf, a flower and a landscape.
- Georgia O'Keeffe New & Some Old - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1933; 2006.6.1158; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view of 4 paintings on wall; signed 'Show Jan Feb 33'Handwritten on verso: "I26a" "12" circled "Show - Jan -Feb. 33"
  Installation view of four O'Keeffe paintings, one of which is on an adjacent wall; 2 paintings of flowers, one abstract landscape and a painting of a barn.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34)- An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1935; 2006.6.1159; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view of 6 paintings on wall; signed on back 'Show Jan Mar - 35'Handwritten on verso: "I27b" "1930" ? "14" circled "?"
  Installation view of six O'Keeffe paintings on a white wall; 2 paintings of New York skyscrapers, a landscape, leaves, and two abstract paintings
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34), An American Place, 1935; 2006.6.1160; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 6 13/16 x 9 3/8 inches; view of 4 paintings on wall one is Black Cross; darkHandwritten on verso: "I28" "14" circled
  Installation view of four O'Keeffe paintings on adjacent white walls; a painting of a jack-in-the-pulpit, a New York harbor scene, a flower and a cross.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34)- An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1935; 2006.6.1161; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 9 15/16 inches; view of 5 paintings on wall one is Black Cross; similar to previous picture different angle of galleryHandwritten on verso: "I29" "14"
  Installation view of five O'Keeffe paintings on adjacent walls; a New York harbor view, an abstract leaf, a black cross, a tree trunk and a barn.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34), An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1935; 2006.6.1162; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; view of 5 paintings on wall; signed on back 'Show Jan Mar - 35'Handwritten on recto: check mark Handwritten on verso: "I 31b" "Show - Jan Mar 35"
  Installation view of five O'Keeffe paintings on adjacent walls; a black cross, a tree trunk, a barn, and two landscapes.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition of Paintings (1919-34)- An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1935; 2006.6.1163; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 5/16 x 9 1/2 inches; view of 4 paintings cropped slightly different than previous pictureHandwritten on verso: "I30" "14" circled
  Installation view of four O'Keeffe paintings on a white wall, a tree trunk, a barn, and two landscapes.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery view, 1937; 2006.6.1164; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 3/16 inches; view of 4 paintings on wall and of large window; black border, wrinkledPrinted on recto: "58 KODAK S AFETY EASTMAN" vertical and reversed Handwritten on verso: "16" "I36a"
  Installation corner view of four O'Keeffe paintings on white walls; Red Hills With Pedernal, White Clouds, 1936, a small New Mexican landscape, Two Pink Shells, 1937, and Red Camellia, 1935.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery view, 1937; 2006.6.1165; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 3 /16 inches; view of 4 paintings on wall and of large windowPrinted on recto: "58 KODAK S AFETY EASTMAN" vertical and reversed Handwritten on recto: three check marks Handwritten on verso: "16" circled"I32"
  Installation view of four O'Keeffe paintings on a white wall; Two White Shells One Black Shell, 1937, My Backyard, 1937, Red Hills With Flowers, 1937, and Cedar Tree With Lavender Hills, 1937.
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery view, 1937; 2006.6.1167; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 2 3/4 inches; cropped photographPrinted on recto: "EASTMAN-SAFETY-KODAK 156" Handwritten on verso: "I34" "9" circled
  Installation view of O'Keeffe's pastel, Red Hills And White Flower, 1937 on a white wall.
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1168; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 5 x 7 1/8 inches; gallery views of exhibition; Caption on wall - 'Photographs by Stieglitz'Handwritten on verso: "I119"
  Interior gallery view of an installation shot of 7 of Stieglitz's framed photographs at the Philadelphia Museum of Art; cloth covered wall, title panel " Photographs by Stieglitz" hangs above the photographs, two vents on baseboards
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1169; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 3/16 inches; gallery views of exhibitionPrinted on recto: "EASTMAN- SAFETY-KODAK 31" Handwritten on verso: "I120"
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1170; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/8 inches; gallery views of exhibition; Caption on wall - 'The Bunch at 291'; de Zayas caricatures of peopleHandwritten on verso: "I121"
  Copyright Philadelphia Museum of Art
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1171; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 3/16 inches; gallery views of exhibition; Caption on pillar - 'Stieglitz looks at the Artists'Handwritten on verso: "I122" "of 6"?
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1172; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/16 inches; gallery views of exhibitionHandwritten on verso: "I123" "3 1/2A"? Stamp on verso: "The following words must accompany any reproduction of this photograph "Courtesy of the PHILADELPHIA MUSEUM OF ART Philadelphia"
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1173; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/8 inches; gallery views of exhibitionHandwritten on verso: "I124" "1/5A" ?" Stamp on verso: "The following words must accompany any reproduction of this photograph "Courtesy of the PHILADELPHIA MUSEUM OF ART Philadelphia"
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1174; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/8 inches; gallery views of exhibition; sticky note 'Greenough'Handwritten on verso: "I125" "1/7"
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1175; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/8 inches; gallery views of exhibition; African MasksHandwritten on verso: "I126"" Stamp on verso: "The following words must accompany any reproduction of this photograph "Courtesy of the PHILADELPHIA MUSEUM OF ART Philadelphia"
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1176; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/8 inches; gallery views of exhibitionPrinted on recto: "EASTMAN-SAFETY-KODAK 23" Handwritten on verso: "I127" "1/6A"
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1177; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/8 inches; gallery views of exhibitionPrinted on recto: "EASTMAN-SAFETY-KODAK 31" Handwritten on verso: "I128" Stamp on verso: "The following words must accompany any reproduction of this photograph "Courtesy of the PHILADELPHIA MUSEUM OF ART Philadelphia"
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1178; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/8 inches; gallery views of exhibitionHandwritten on verso: "I129"
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1179; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/8 inches; gallery views of exhibitionPrinted on recto: "EASTMAN-SAFETY-KODAK 31" Handwritten on verso: "I130" Stamp on verso: "The following words must accompany any reproduction of this photograph "Courtesy of the PHILADELPHIA MUSEUM OF ART Philadelphia"
- History of An American, Alfred Stieglitz, Stieglitz '291' and After, Philadelphia Museum of Art. Interior Gallery View, after 1949; 2006.6.1180; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 x 7 1/8 inches; gallery views of exhibitionPrinted on recto: "EASTMAN-SAFETY-KODAK 31" Handwritten on verso: "I131"
- John Marin Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1945-1946; 2006.6.1181; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 7/8 x 4 inches; gallery views of exhibition
  Installation views of nine of John Marin's paintings as seen from adjacent rooms.
- John Marin Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1945-1946; 2006.6.1182; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 7/8 x 10 inches; copy of 2006-06-1183Label on verso: "AS Philadelphia 1944, 1945 304"
  Installation views of nine of John Marin's paintings as seen on adjacent walls.
- John Marin Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1945-1946; 2006.6.1183; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 13/16 x 4 inches; gallery views of exhibition
  Installation views of nine of John Marin's paintings as seen from adjacent walls.
- John Marin Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1945-1946; 2006.6.1184; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 13/16 x 3 15/16 inches; gallery views of exhibition
  Installation views of five of John Marin's paintings as seen from adjacent walls.
- John Marin Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1945-1946; 2006.6.1185; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 13/16 x 3 15/16 inches; gallery views of exhibition
  Installation view of a collection of photographs on a white wall.
- John Marin Exhibition - An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1945-1946; 2006.6.1186; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 1/16 x 5 7/16 inches; gallery views of exhibitionPrinted on recto: "AGFA NITRATE FILM" (vertical, reversed)
- Georgia O'Keeffe Paintings 1946-50, An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1950; 2006.6.1202; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 7/16 x 8 1/2 inches; gallery views of exhibitionHandwritten on verso: "I52", "DTG 50", "1082-14"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Paintings 1946-50, An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1950; 2006.6.1203; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 7/16 x 8 1/2 inches; gallery views of exhibitionHandwritten on verso: "I53", "DTG 50 ", "1081 X21"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Paintings 1946-50, An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1950; 2006.6.1204; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; gallery views of exhibitionPrinted on recto: "ANSCO SAFETY FILM 3" (reverse) Handwritten on verso: "I54", "DTG 50", "13-6 ILAZO EL"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Paintings 1946-50, An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1950; 2006.6.1205; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 10 inches; gallery views of exhibitionHandwritten on verso: "I59", "DTG 50 ", "10-5+ES" (?)
- Georgia O'Keeffe Paintings 1946-50, An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1950; 2006.6.1206; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; gallery views of exhibitionPrinted on recto: "5 ANSCO SAFETY FILM" (reverse) Handwritten on verso: "I61", "DTG 50", "20A 63 1 to 18"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Paintings 1946-50, An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1950; 2006.6.1207; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 9/16 x 9 5/8 inches; gallery views of exhibitionHandwritten on verso: "I56", "DTG 50 ", "62-3", "11" (circled)
- Georgia O'Keeffe Paintings 1946-50, An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1950; 2006.6.1208; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 7/8 x 10 inches; gallery views of exhibition; Handwritten on verso: 'From 1950 Show folder - Holmes [illegible]Handwritten on verso: "I57", "DTG 50 ", "13X 12", "13"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Paintings 1946-50, An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1950; 2006.6.1209; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 1/2 x 8 1/2 inches; On verso in O'Keeffe's handwriting: From 1950 Show folder - Holmes [illegible]Handwritten on verso: "I58", "DTG 50 ", "From 1930 Show folder - Holeues Barry Treeuks With Snow -46", "W84"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Paintings 1946-50, An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1950; 2006.6.1210; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 7/16 x 8 1/2 inches; gallery views of exhibitionHandwritten on verso: "I55", "DTG 50 ", "1099-10-"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Paintings 1946-50, An American Place, Interior Gallery View, 1950; 2006.6.1211; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 7/8 x 10 inches; gallery views of exhibitionHandwritten on verso: "I60", "DTG 50 "
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at Downtown Gallery, 1952; 2006.6.1212; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 3/4 x 9 7/8 inches; On verso: Oliver Baker stamp and handwritten: 'opposite wall to where you come in toward street and windows.'Handwritten on verso: 'opposite wall to where you come in- toward street+ windows.' "I62" "17" Stamp on verso: "OLIVER BAKER 27 WEST 15th ST. NEW YORK 11, N.Y. FILE No 9746 Chelsea 3-4661"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at Downtown Gallery, 1952; 2006.6.1213; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 8 1/16 x 9 15/16 inches; On verso: Oliver Baker stamp and handwritten: 'paintings face top of stairs paintings face window'Handwritten on verso: "I63 DTG 52", "3 painting face top of stairs 2 dtgs face window", "Wave 1921.", "Riuz Carolina" (?), "1945" Stamp on verso: "OLIVER BAKER 27 WEST 15th ST. NEW YORK 11, N.Y. FILE No 9747 Chelsea 3-4661"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at Downtown Gallery, 1952; 2006.6.1214; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 7/16 x 10 inches; On verso: Oliver Baker stamp and handwritten: 'As you come in looking to right wall'Handwritten on verso: "I64 DTG 52", "As you come in, looking to left wall", "P.Sipeas"(?), "1927", "Sun., water- Maine 1922" Stamp on verso: "OLIVER BAKER 27 WEST 15th ST. NEW YORK 11, N.Y. FILE No 9744 Chelsea 3-4661"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at Downtown Gallery, 1952; 2006.6.1215; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 1/8 x 10 inches; On verso: Oliver Baker stamp and handwritten: 'As you come in looking to left wall'Handwritten on verso: "I65", "17" (circled), "As you come in, looking to right wall" Stamp on verso: "OLIVER BAKER 27 WEST 15th ST. NEW YORK 11, N.Y. FILE No 9745 Chelsea 3-4661"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at Downtown Gallery, circa 1960s; 2006.6.1216; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 9/16 x 10 1/16 inches; Oliver Baker stamp on versoHandwritten on verso: "I66 DTG 61" Stamp on verso: "Oliver Baker Photography 25 Washingtion Sq. No. New York 11, N. Y. 33-464 ORegon 4-5080"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at Downtown Gallery, circa 1960s; 2006.6.1217; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 3/4 x 10 inches; Oliver Baker stamp on versoHandwritten on verso: "I67 DTG 61" Stamp on verso: "Oliver Baker Photography 25 Washingtion Sq. No. New York 11, N. Y. 33-465 ORegon 4-5080"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at Downtown Gallery, circa 1960s; 2006.6.1218; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 6 5/8 x 10 inches; Oliver Baker stamp on versoHandwritten on verso: "I68 DTG 61" Stamp on verso: "Oliver Baker Photography 25 Washingtion Sq. No. New York 11, N. Y. 33-466 ORegon 4-5080"
- Georgia O'Keeffe Exhibition at Amon Carter Museum, 1956; 2006.6.1219; Amon Carter Museum of Western Art; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 7 7/8 x 10 inches; Amon Carter Museum stamp on versoHandwritten on verso: "I69" Stamp on verso: "NOTICE This photograph purposes only. It must not be reproduced or publicy exhibited in any way without the ownwer of the work photographed. Amon Carter Museum Fort Worth, Texas"